okay so we have dispatched instruction
in Rob 5 its value that it will produce
is minus 1 that value will be broadcast
in cycle 7 because it begins executed at
six but before we get to that in cycle 6
we are going to issue this instruction
in cycle 6 we have finished our
multiplication here it was executing in
cycles three four and five took three
cycles so in cycle 6 it also broadcast
the result so the result of the
multiplication is broadcast as a 8 under
the name of Rob tool and this is marked
as done Rob to value is captured this
aid is going to be captured here because
we were waiting for up to here we are
not waiting for up to so everything is
fine in cycle 7 the rob 5 instruction
broadcast the result of minus 1 this
minus one gets captured here because it
matches this and this instruction is
done in cycle 7 as we have seen we have
written this result captured it here we
have marked this instruction as done we
have nothing left to issue so the
question for you is in what cycle do we
dispatch this instruction